<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Learning on Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep Learning on Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Use Tina.io CMS</title>
      <link>https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/use-tina-cms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/use-tina-cms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you prefer managing your site using a CMS? Or would you like to make it easier for someone (a non-techie, perhaps) in your team to make edits easily? If interested, follow along. Else, skip to the &lt;a href=&#34;../organize-content/&#34;&gt;next section&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let&#39;s sync your site with Tina CMS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;prerequisites-&#34; class=link_owner&gt;&#xA;  Prerequisites !!&#xA;  &lt;a href=&#34;#prerequisites-&#34; class=&#34;link icon&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;svg&gt;&#xA;      &lt;use xlink:href=&#34;#anchor-link&#34;&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/svg&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obviously you ought to have &lt;strong&gt;a github account&lt;/strong&gt;. This is where your website source will live. Basically, Tina will read from github and write (commit) to your github repo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shortcodes</title>
      <link>https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/shortcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jawad.dev/docs/dl/shortcodes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Instead of writing all your site pages from scratch, Hugo lets you define and use &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/&#34;&gt;shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why shortcodes? While markdown is sufficient to produce simple pages, it&#39;s insufficient where complex page structures are needed. Thusly, whenever we need special styling, shortcodes compliment the shortcomings of markdown.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This way, you can side step complex html and css boilerplate in your content files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, the shortcode will wrap content, sometimes it won&#39;t. When content is wrapped, a closing shortcode tag is needed. Please see the link I provided above and the markdown files for examples. You&#39;ll get the gist pretty quickly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
